[
	{
		"question": "What song this lyrics is for `Like neon inside the glass`\n1)**Morph**\n2)**Bandito**\n3)**Neon Gravestones**\n4)Leave The City",
		"answers": ["Bandito"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who Has Been Seen Peeing From The Band Members?\n1)**Tyler**\n2)**Josh**\n3)**Ned**\n4)**Tyler and Josh**",
		"answers": ["Tyler And Josh"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many tracks does Trench contain?\n1)**13**\n2)**14**\n3)**15**\n4)**12**",
		"answers": ["14", "Fourteen"]
	}
	,
	{
		"question": "How many tracks does Scaled and Icy contain?\n1)**13**\n2)**12**\n3)**10**\n4)**11**",
		"answers": ["11", "eleven"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many tracks does Blurryface contain?\n1)**14**\n2)**12**\n3)**10**\n4)**13**",
		"answers": ["14", "fourteen"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many times the chorus is repeated in Redecorate?\n1)**3**\n2)**2**\n3)**4**\n4)**5**",
		"answers": ["3", "three"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What date did Scaled and Icy release?\n1)**May 23 , 2021**\n2)**May 21 , 2021**\n3)**April 23 , 2021**\n4)**April 21 , 2021**",
		"answers": ["May 21 , 2021", "May 21","21 May" , "21 may , 2021"]
	},
	{
		"question": "____ Gravestones",
		"answers": ["Neon"]
	},
	{
		"question": "____ Away",
		"answers": ["Shy"]
	},
	{
		"question": "____ Radio",
		"answers": ["car"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Kitchen ____",
		"answers": ["sink"]
	},
	{
		"question": "____ Eyes",
		"answers": ["glowing"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Before You ____ Your",
		"answers": ["start"]
	},
	{
		"question": "March to the ____",
		"answers": ["Sea"]
	},
	{
		"question": "____ with a Pen",
		"answers": ["addict"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Lyrics: *Should I Keep it on ____*",
		"answers": ["display"]
	}
]

	
